<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Report A on CSE Thesis Musings</title><link>/docs/report-a/</link><description>Recent content in Report A on CSE Thesis Musings</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href="https://featherbear.cc">Andrew Wong (z5206677)&lt;/a></copyright><atom:link href="/docs/report-a/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>/docs/report-a/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/introduction/</guid><description>The adoption of consumer-grade Internet of Things (IoT) devices has been both widespread and constantly growing. With demands for such devices growing by 12% each year (Research &amp;amp; Markets 2021), this AU$130B industry has cordially invited thousands of households to invest in smart devices such as light bulbs, fans, televisions and fridges.</description></item><item><title>Background</title><link>/docs/report-a/background/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/background/</guid><description>The consumer market has experienced an abundance of IoT devices, largely attributed to the presence of IoT manufacturers who offer white-label partnerships with resellers to provide “custom” products. Through these partnerships, vendors buy into the IoT manufacturer’s ecosystem - namely being the product itself, the companion smartphone application, and the cloud infrastructure supporting backend communications - all without requiring vendors to posses any knowledge or understanding of how to design, develop nor manufacture the IoT products that they sell.</description></item><item><title>Literature Review</title><link>/docs/report-a/literature-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/literature-review/</guid><description>TODO: Application?
TODO: Application?
TODO: Application?
TODO: Application?
TODO: Application?
TODO: Application?
TODO: Application?
IoT | 2018 - Michael Steigerwald (VTRUST) In 2018 the security research group VTRUST (2018) analysed a line of white-labelled IoT product revisions based from the IoT manufacturer Tuya.</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/report-a/proposal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/proposal/</guid><description>Previous Achievements * Smartphone application reverse engineering * Device firmware interception * Device hardware and component identification * Network traffic analysis * Storage analysis Unaddressed Areas * Post-2019 replication study * In-depth firmware analysis @{fi12020027} outlines a list of things to look out for during analysis # Statement How have manufacturers of IoT / smart home devices addressed the increasing concerns of digital privacy and product security?</description></item></channel></rss>