<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Report A on CSE Thesis Musings</title><link>/docs/report-a/</link><description>Recent content in Report A on CSE Thesis Musings</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href="https://featherbear.cc">Andrew Wong (z5206677)&lt;/a></copyright><atom:link href="/docs/report-a/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Glossary of Acronyms</title><link>/docs/report-a/acronyms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/acronyms/</guid><description> (e)MMC - (Embedded) Multi Media Card - i.e. flash storage IoT - Internet of Things UGC - User Generated Content PII - Personally Identifiable Information SoC - System on Chip References</description></item><item><title>1 \| Introduction</title><link>/docs/report-a/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/introduction/</guid><description>Introduction Consumer grade Internet of Things (IoT) devices have become widely adopted with continuously growing demand. With demands for such devices growing by 12% each year (Research &amp;amp; Markets 2021), this AU$130B industry has cordially invited thousands of households to invest in smart devices such as light bulbs, fans, televisions and fridges.</description></item><item><title>2 \| Background</title><link>/docs/report-a/background/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/background/</guid><description>Background The widespread availability of IoT The consumer market has experienced a large influx of IoT devices, largely attributed to the presence of IoT manufacturers who offer white-label partnerships with resellers to provide “custom” products. Through these partnerships, vendors buy into the IoT manufacturer’s ecosystem - namely being the product itself, the companion smartphone application, and the cloud infrastructure supporting backend communications - all without requiring vendors to posses any knowledge or understanding of how to design, develop nor manufacture the IoT products that they sell.</description></item><item><title>3 \| Literature Review</title><link>/docs/report-a/literature-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/literature-review/</guid><description>Literature Review Broad security study of Tuya-based devices In 2018 the security research group VTRUST (2018) analysed a line of white-labelled IoT product revisions based from the IoT manufacturer Tuya. Despite claims of ‘military-grade security’, basic packet logging of network activity concluded that “the analysis of the ‘smart’ devices using this basic platform is generally frightening”, with “serious […] shortcomings”.</description></item><item><title>4 \| Thesis Plan</title><link>/docs/report-a/proposal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/proposal/</guid><description>Thesis Plan Statement With the widespread availability of IoT devices, there is large interest in exploring how manufacturers of IoT / smart home devices have addressed the increasing concerns of digital privacy and product security. This thesis aims to explore the stance and measures that Roborock has taken regarding privacy policies and security concerns in their Roborock S6 robot vacuum cleaner.</description></item><item><title>5 \| Preliminary Results</title><link>/docs/report-a/progress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/progress/</guid><description>Preliminary Results Network Setup [Initial] Packet Capture No LAN-LAN packets??? incomplete test - misconfigured packet capture setup Teardown Initial Breakdown and Pinout (where needed) STM32, Allwinner R16 (Quad-core ARMv7 processor), USB Port (custom ADB?)
Identification of the UART pins Serial Access Serial (baud=115200) gives us a shell!</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/report-a/bibliography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/bibliography/</guid><description>TODO: Migrate to LaTeX or somthing hehe -- References</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/report-a/conclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/report-a/conclusion/</guid><description>TODO: Migrate to LaTeX or somthing hehe -- References</description></item></channel></rss>